Mom, I will tell you.
You will speak.  What did you say?
I ordered some products from Doodup
which also included my son's toys.
And there are some very useful things used in the house
which I have ordered.
My mother's gift has arrived.   It is
very heavy and very
big.
Yes, the
child has opened [nasal sound] so he gets
happy with this too
[laughs]
this is the shoe rack, this is the type of shoe rack to be made,
it will have to be assembled and maybe
I have written four layer on it, yes,
four layer shoe rack, this is the
doctor kit I had ordered for my daughter.  Look at its price,
this is a light at such a low price.
Look at its price, it is so low.
Now when you turn off all these lights etc.
then you will see this type of
light in the darkness.  You like
this ginger laughing.  Meaning, this is a
very useful thing for the kitchen.  Got it here at such a
low price.  I didn't even think about it.
I have ordered this
two in one vegetable cutter.  I mean, now that
winter has arrived, more green vegetables will be cooked
at home.  Like fenugreek vegetable has been prepared.  The
spinach vegetable is ready.  You
can lock it by doing this.  We will remove this from here
and whatever else is there will just cut from the side and
fall down.  What is this?
Bash.  Wow.
Wow mom, what's in it?  Wow, this is such a
beautiful product
brother, I really wanted this,
I was thinking of buying it for a long time, I mean
when we do makeup in front of the mirror, there is a lot of
problem and there is no cell in it, if we
put the cell here then these
lights of the makeup mirror will turn on
and this is a vacuum one, you will get a
vacuum on the mirror, just
stick both of these [music] and a
vacuum will be created there and come on, this is also a very good and
useful product.  And I
ordered this to correct the shape of the back.
This is the band.  Look at its price, it
is so surprising.
This is the type of band that comes.  You should go and
see if this was of much use to mom?  Mom
got a book for you along with the doctor kit.
Book?
Yes, here is the book.
Maybe he will put the book inside it.  Battery: Yes,
these people have not given the battery.  You will have to put the battery in it,
mom.  And then the child can
keep it aside like this and explain it.   I
will show you later after putting the battery in it.  Let's
see the next one brother.  This is the
most useful thing in your kitchen.  This is
fruit juice.  Now what's in it?
You can keep pouring water on top comfortably.  Water will keep coming out from the bottom
and whatever we cook,
whatever our pulses are, whatever edible
items, they will be stored inside it, they will come out and
keep in the sink as well, brother,
I have ordered this wallet, this is a card holder, this is a
special card, you
can keep as many cards in it, you can also keep as much cash as you want,
Multani Mitti worth ₹ is only for
₹8 and this is pure Multani Mitti and
this is a very trust worthy brand, this brand is
working since 1994 [screaming voice],
now I will show you such a useful
thing which is very useful, means it comes in
handy sometime or the other.  Look, this
is a pouch to keep the food.  Meaning, whenever it happens that
you feel that it is about to rain and
you have to go out of the house at that time, then
this pouch comes.
You can put your cell phone inside this pouch and then you
can go out in the rain comfortably.  You can wet
your phone.  Absolutely nothing will happen to the
phone.  I ordered a book for my baby called
Water Book.  Ok?  What's in this Water Book
?  There are some such sheets.  I mean, this
is some drawing.  Ok?  You can see that
some are visible and some are invisible sheets.
So what happens in such a situation is that
you have to refill water in this pen.
So when you
do this, like this, like this, then their color will come, whatever it is,
I
mean the carbon stickers, even after you turn off the light, they will still be
seen shining separately.  So let's turn off the lights and see if
we can see anything shining here or
not.
It will look something like this, meaning it is becoming
completely dark for us now.
But these stickers will look something like this.
Full tight pouch.  You
can also keep liquid items inside it.  Whatever salty doll
you keep, air should
not enter inside it.  You can put those types of things in it and
keep it closed.  Next I
ordered this cobweb cleaner.  Oh, this will be
assembled right here.  Wait son, will you
take this too?  Look, it has very nice
fur.  And what is its length?  Yes,
you can increase the length to any extent.  Oh brother,
its lust is very strong.
[screaming sound]
He's grown up, brother.  I am not able to show it to you
in the video.  I can't show it in the video.  He is
very stubborn.  It
seemed very big.
Ordered it.
Yes, I ordered it for you only.
Mom, I am telling you this.
This is a product of just ₹4.  C can also be cleaned.  You
can also clean it with wash gram flour.
And it was only for ₹4.  This is the
next product which I found to be very hygienic.
Meaning that the sponge also came free.
And you have to press it like this on the inside side, so
brother, now this is going to go into our kitchen.
I had seen it on other sides.
Its rate was 1100 1200 1300 or so rupees.
Ok?  But here I
got this machine only at this price.
[laughs]
Brother, you should really
not do any unboxing with children.
[laughter]
[screaming]
Wow, I saw it.
You can try using a plastic bag with this.  I
will see how to
use it and I will also share its review with you whether it was
useful for me
or not.  They don't know what to say.
Reel speaks perhaps.  Some of these reels have also
arrived.  This is controlling.
You can also control it by placing your foot on it.  You
can control it by placing your hands.  And here is
its plug.  I ordered these cookie cutters.
Meaning, inside it you can see
circle, star, so four types of shapes are
inside it.  My daughter is a bit
naughty.  I mean, almost everyone's
children must be so gluttonous as my daughter.  I
can make cookies of this type of shape and give them to my child.
Then I can make rotis and give them to you.
If it is a big peeler.  Ok?
And I don't know for how long I wanted this.
This is enough.  I mean, I wouldn't say it's
very good material.
Its material is good.
Ok.  I have ordered this sponge.
Meaning, by holding it, we
can easily clean the bathroom tiles and the bathroom floor.  But next
I have ordered this Lassi or
mostly in our house Kadhi Khati this type
of vegetable is made more often.  I mean, we are a bit
desi people, so things like Kadhi
Vadi and these types of things are made more in our house.  So it
works that way.
I ordered this.
You should see its price.  And these books are
for multipurpose.
Meaning you can also keep your jewellery inside it.
But why does it feel a bit tight to me?  The
quality of its plastic is good.
This is something like this type of box.  Ok?  And
you can keep your cut fruits etc. inside it.  You
can cut and keep the vegetables.
You can chop your vegetables and
keep them separately.  Like it has onion and
tomato.  Ok?  And whatever
vegetables you have, cut them and keep them inside it.  This is
made from a separate bundle.  So let's
unbox it.  There are
probably some small things inside it too, which are two-two or
three-pointed things, maybe it might be that
or this scrubber which was quite small in size,
I had ordered it.
[laughter]
Okay, there's a little steel [nasal sound]
strainer that we have to
put inside the sink.  So
whatever dirt is there, it gets stored inside it.
And your problem of sink blockage gets resolved.   I
ordered this Maggi.  Like it shows the lyrics of the 70s.
But it doesn't look like the 70s inside.  It does
n't seem more than bound to
me.
[screaming sound]
Next is the eye mask.  There is no gel inside it.
You have to keep it inside the refrigerator.
When it cools down,
I ordered this lighter which is very useful.
So, this is a glass that protects the eyes.
When, for example, firecrackers are burnt or
dust is flying somewhere or something else, it
seems that brother, you may have a problem.
So
this type of glasses to protect your eyes.  [MUSIC] There are tips
inside where you can try your own things.
This is a small light.
Got it at such a low price.  If you have a small child with you, then you should
not make it completely dark at night
because if you do not tell anything then the
child may face some problem.  The
sealing machine will have to insert the cell.
After inserting the cell, it has to be closed like this.  So
this will seal your pouch.  This is light.
This is how it's going on in the dark.
Wow mom.   If
you liked it, then you would hang it like this for them to think.
I ordered one for shagun,
it is very useful. Suppose you are going somewhere
and you have to give shagun to someone, then
if you put it in these types of cards, then
I think it looks very impressive. When
you put even one of these,
you will not feel it at all. I had
shown you a raincoat. Okay, so I thought brother, let me
see what kind of raincoat is available at such a low price. So
brother, this is exactly like a foil. It is a very
thin foil. I think
with this, I will have to cover the AC etc., so
this will be
useful in that. Look at the shape, oh ho ho, I have made the sleeves and have
given this complete cap also.
Next, let's see what our chipku is. Yes,
brother, this is a strip which is very useful
for girls. This is an extension
holder. Okay, you can sometimes stick it on the wall anywhere.
You can stick the extension inside it.
So this is wallet
freshener jasmine flavor.  And this is where
I smell something really nice.  21 was the
clutch which had the material on it.
So quality wise I
liked it a little less.  Rest looks wise it
is good.  Now let's unbox these lights and
see.
I have
this [squeaking sound] this is mine
yes this is yours no
[nasal sound] let's turn it
on and see.  ton ton
wow red colour
count [screaming voice] colour total I
ordered four lights, okay these are for my daughter, she is a
baby so a couple of things
seemed expensive to me and when I bought them, these
people showed me ₹300 tax separately, they are
charging ₹300 extra,
they had a different delivery system, I mean
understand this, approximately ₹300 to ₹350, from ₹350 it
may reach ₹400 also, they
charge so much extra money.  So this much
margin is left on so many products.
But if this machine is ready then it is
available here for Rs 1100, 120, 1300.  But it is
available here for just under Rs 600.
So after seeing these types of things
I thought it's okay to watch it.  So much
charge etc. is being taken.  So no problem.
Rest, when I try using these things personally,
then I
will share that review with you also.
I really liked the duped products.
Say like, share, subscribe, say it loudly while looking there
[screaming sound]
next it
becomes worthy for momma,
momma brought a rhythmic one, I will
not give you to anyone, I will
not give you to anyone, hmm